Hello, English learners.
你好，英语学习者。
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我叫Marco。
And my name is Kathryn and today we're talking about being clean.
我叫Kathryn，今天我们聊聊保持清洁这件事。
Yeah, we're going to be doing the laundry, right?
是啊，我们要讲洗衣服，对吧？
It's a very important part of everyone's weekly schedule.
这是每个人每周日程中非常重要的一部分。
And not only important, but I find it to be a little bit difficult because, you know,
不仅重要，而且我觉得还有点难，因为你知道，
like washing machine and what clothes you should mix with what, you know, how much detergent
比如洗衣机、什么衣服该混在一起洗、该放多少洗衣粉，
and how long.
还有洗多久。
It's such a complicated process.
真是个复杂的过程。
Well, let's say this, it might not be difficult, but it's very easy to mess up.
嗯，这么说吧，可能不难，但很容易搞砸。
Exactly.
没错。
Yeah, that's the problem.
是啊，问题就在这儿。
It's very easy to like just ruin your favorite t-shirt if you don't do laundry correctly.
如果洗衣不当，很容易就把你最喜欢的T恤给毁了。
Or all of your white socks turn pink, for example.
或者所有白袜子都变成粉色，比如这样。
Right.
对。
So we're going to be looking at a lot of vocabulary and phrases related to this topic.
所以我们要学习很多与这个话题相关的词汇和短语。
And before we get started with the dialogue, why don't we take a look at vocabulary preview?
在开始对话之前，我们先来看看词汇预览吧？
Vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
Okay, so central to all of these phrases and words that we're going to be hearing is a
好的，所有这些短语和词汇的核心是一个东西，
thing, an electric thing that helps us wash our clothes.
一个帮助我们洗衣服的电器。
Right, a washing machine.
对，洗衣机。
Right, pretty simple, right?
对，很简单，对吧？
So washing is to wash, washing and machine.
所以“washing”是洗，“machine”是机器。
So they go together, washing machine.
它们合在一起就是洗衣机。
Right.
对。
So it's easy now, you just put all your clothes in this thing and it washes it for you.
现在很简单了，你只要把所有衣服放进去，它就会帮你洗好。
Now, you know, a lot of people don't like to use washing machines.
不过，很多人不喜欢用洗衣机。
They say it doesn't really clean the clothes as well as doing it by hand.
他们说洗衣机不如手洗得干净。
Really?
真的吗？
Well, I'd say most clothes get washed pretty well with a washing machine.
嗯，我觉得大多数衣服用洗衣机洗得挺好的。
But if you have those hard to get stains or some dirt, maybe it's good to have a washing
但如果你有那些难去除的污渍或脏东西，也许用个
board.
搓衣板会更好。
A washing board, yeah.
搓衣板，是啊。
Yeah, where you can really scrub it yourself.
对，你可以自己使劲搓。
And well, funny you mentioned that word stain because it's our second word that we're going
嗯，你提到“stain”这个词真巧，因为这是我们
to preview, a stain.
要预览的第二个词，stain（污渍）。
Right, a stain is some color, maybe some food or wine or grass that you can't remove from
对，污渍就是一些颜色，可能是食物、酒或草，你没法从
your clothes.
衣服上去掉。
Right.
对。
So it's very common.
所以很常见。
You're having a nice dinner and all of a sudden you spill wine on your shirt.
你正享用一顿美餐，突然把酒洒在衬衫上。
So you have a wine stain.
于是就有了酒渍。
I hate that.
我讨厌那样。
And you can also have stain on your, you can also have a stain on your carpet, right?
你也可以在地毯上有污渍，对吧？
So if you spill some coffee on your carpet, it's got a little circle that's brown forever.
所以如果你把咖啡洒在地毯上，就会留下一个永远去不掉的棕色小圆圈。
Right?
对吧？
Or even some people have stained the teeth, right?
甚至有些人的牙齿也有污渍，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
So you can get them turned back white with a little money to your dentist.
所以你可以花点钱找牙医，把它们变回白色。
Exactly.
正是。
So those are the two words that we're going to be looking at today in Vocabulary Preview.
这就是我们今天在词汇预览中要看的两个词。
So let's listen to our dialogue.
那么我们来听对话吧。
Let's see what's happening with these people that are doing laundry.
看看这些洗衣服的人发生了什么。
Okay, let's go through this one more time.
好的，我们再来一遍。
I don't want any more ruined or dyed blouses.
我不想再有任何被染坏或染色的衬衫了。
I know, I know.
我知道，我知道。
Okay.
好的。
So I had to separate the colors from the whites and put them in this strange looking contraption
所以我得把彩色衣服和白色衣服分开，放进这个看起来怪怪的
so-called washing machine.
所谓的洗衣机里。
Right.
对。
You have to turn it on and program it depending on what type of clothes you're washing.
你得打开它，根据你洗的衣服类型来设定程序。
For example, for delicates, you should set a shorter washing cycle.
比如，对于精致衣物，你应该设置较短的洗涤周期。
Also be sure to use fabric softener and this detergent when washing.
洗的时候还要记得用柔顺剂和这种洗衣粉。
So complicated.
真复杂。
Okay.
好的。
What about this red wine stain?
那这个红酒渍怎么办？
How do I get it out?
我怎么才能去掉它？
Since this is a white t-shirt, you can just pour a little bit of bleach on it and it will
因为这是件白T恤，你可以倒一点漂白剂在上面，
do the trick.
就能搞定。
Cool.
酷。
Then I can just throw everything in the dryer for an hour and it's all set, right?
那我就可以把所有东西扔进烘干机烘一小时，就都好了，对吧？
No.
不行。
Since you're washing delicates and cotton, you should set the dryer to medium heat and
因为你洗的是精致衣物和棉质衣物，你应该把烘干机设为中温，
for 20 minutes.
烘20分钟。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'll just have everything dry cleaned.
我还是全拿去干洗吧。
Okay, so we've got someone who is maybe doing the laundry for the first time and he's not
好的，看来有个人可能是第一次洗衣服，
really understanding the instructions he's got.
他不太理解收到的指示。
Well, that's the thing I tell you.
嗯，我跟你说，就是这样。
It's a little bit difficult and well, it's very tedious at times to try and do laundry
有点难，而且有时候这样洗衣服
like this.
很繁琐。
Well, the first thing that's maybe tedious about it is that you have to really worry
嗯，可能第一件繁琐的事是你得担心
about what colors go together.
什么颜色能混在一起。
Right.
对。
So let's take a look at those words that were related to doing laundry now in Language Takeaway.
那么现在我们来看看语言要点中与洗衣相关的那些词。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay, the first word we have is actually related to a joke we made earlier about pink socks.
好的，第一个词其实跟我们之前开的粉色袜子的玩笑有关。
So if you change the color of something, you're dying it.
所以如果你改变某物的颜色，你就是在染色。
Okay, die.
好的，dye（染色）。
So it's pronounced exactly the same way as, you know, to die, to not live anymore.
它的发音和“die”（死亡）完全一样。
Die.
Die。
But it's spelled differently.
但拼写不同。
D-Y-E.
D-Y-E。
Okay, so it can be a verb or an adjective.
好的，它可以是动词或形容词。
Or an noun.
也可以是名词。
Or a noun.
或者名词。
So something that you put on clothes to change the color is called a dye.
所以用来改变衣服颜色的东西叫做染料。
A dye.
染料。
But to do this, to change the color of some clothes is to dye the clothes.
但做这件事，改变衣服的颜色，就是给衣服染色。
So that's maybe what happens when you wash a red t-shirt with all your white t-shirts.
所以这可能就是当你把红T恤和所有白T恤一起洗时发生的事。
Then you have dyed shirts.
然后你就有了染色的衬衫。
You have pink shirts and...
你有了粉色衬衫，还有……
And also women, when they go to the beauty salon, they dye their hair.
还有女人去美容院时，她们会染头发。
Exactly.
没错。
So to change the color of your hair, it means it's a long-term change.
所以改变头发的颜色，意味着是长期改变。
It's not short.
不是短期的。
It's not like one day.
不是一天两天。
It means probably for a long time.
可能意味着很长时间。
So that's the correct word, to dye.
所以正确的词是“to dye”。
Very different.
很不一样。
Maybe some people say to paint, which, you know, we understand, but the correct form
也许有些人会说“to paint”，我们也能理解，但正确的形式
would be to dye.
应该是“to dye”。
And next we have a word that describes a certain kind of clothing.
接下来我们有一个词，描述一种特定的衣物。
We're not talking about pants or socks.
我们说的不是裤子或袜子。
We're talking about delicates.
我们说的是精致衣物。
Delicates.
精致衣物。
So now this adjective, delicate, which means it's very... easy to break.
所以这个形容词“delicate”，意思是它非常……容易损坏。
Fragile, right?
易碎，对吧？
But this is a noun, delicates.
但这是个名词，“delicates”。
Right.
对。
So you think of something that's easy to break or to ruin, maybe you think of underwear.
所以你会想到一些容易弄坏或毁掉的东西，也许你会想到内衣。
Underwear.
内衣。
You know, underwear is something you wear under your clothing and so it's generally
你知道，内衣是穿在衣服里面的，所以通常
not as strong as a shirt or a pair of jeans.
不像衬衫或牛仔裤那么结实。
And so we call these in English delicates.
所以我们在英语中称这些为“精致衣物”。
Very good.
很好。
So you have to be careful when you're washing your delicates because it's happened to me
所以你在洗精致衣物时要小心，因为我就遇到过
before.
这种情况。
You know, you come in with all the clothes and then you have stretched out boxers or
你知道，你把所有衣服放进去，然后发现平角内裤被拉松了
something like that.
或者类似的情况。
Yeah.
是啊。
So that's why many women, I know, wash delicates by hand.
所以我知道很多女性会手洗精致衣物。
So you separate the clothes from the delicates.
所以你要把普通衣服和精致衣物分开。
Very good.
很好。
And now if you're washing delicates or you're washing towels or t-shirts, it's always a
现在，如果你在洗精致衣物、毛巾或T恤，使用
good idea to use fabric softener.
衣物柔顺剂总是一个好主意。
All right, fabric softener.
好的，衣物柔顺剂。
What are these two words?
这两个词是什么意思？
One of them you understand already.
其中一个你已经懂了。
Maybe it's soft, softener.
可能是“柔软”，柔顺剂。
So it makes it soft.
所以它让东西变柔软。
Yeah.
是的。
Something that makes something softer.
让东西变得更柔软的东西。
We've got fabric softener.
我们有衣物柔顺剂。
It's something that makes the clothes that you wash softer.
它能让洗的衣服变得更柔软。
So fabric is any type of material, right?
所以“fabric”是指任何类型的材料，对吧？
Like a textile.
像纺织品。
Yeah.
是的。
So it could be cotton or silk or nylon, linen.
所以可以是棉、丝、尼龙、亚麻。
So these are all kinds of fabrics.
这些都是不同类型的布料。
So you pour a little bit of this in your washing machine and your clothes come out really nice
所以你在洗衣机里倒一点这个，衣服洗出来就会非常
and soft.
柔软。
It feels nice just talking about it.
光是说说就觉得舒服。
All right.
好的。
And well, also to wash your clothes, to actually make them clean, you use detergent.
还有，要洗衣服，真正把它们洗干净，你会用洗衣粉。
Right.
对。
So many people might want to say the word soap because soap is what we use to wash our
很多人可能会想说“肥皂”这个词，因为肥皂是我们用来洗
hands and our dishes.
手和洗碗的东西。
But here we have detergent.
但这里我们用的是“洗衣粉”。
So this is a special soap for your clothes.
所以这是一种专门洗衣服的肥皂。
Right.
对。
Laundry detergent.
洗衣粉。
Yeah.
是的。
You could just say laundry.
你可以只说“laundry”。
You could say laundry detergent or simply detergent.
你可以说“laundry detergent”或者简单说“detergent”。
And now in order to remove those nasty stains that maybe are very hard, you would use a
现在，为了去除那些可能很难洗掉的顽固污渍，你会用
chemical called bleach.
一种叫漂白剂的化学物质。
All right.
好的。
So bleach is the dangerous chemical because it smells very strong.
所以漂白剂是一种危险的化学物质，因为它气味很刺鼻。
Right.
对。
And it can change the color of your clothes to white or yellow.
而且它能把衣服的颜色变成白色或黄色。
So we usually only use bleach with white clothes.
所以我们通常只对白色衣服使用漂白剂。
I actually had a friend who changed the color of his hair to white using bleach.
我有个朋友用漂白剂把头发颜色变成了白色。
He put bleach on his head and on his hair and it just turned white.
他把漂白剂涂在头上和头发上，头发就变白了。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
So many people do that because they want to go from dark colors to light colors.
很多人这么做，因为他们想从深色变成浅色。
And in that case, you wouldn't say, you could say that he dyed his hair white, but usually
在这种情况下，你不会说，你可以说他染白了头发，但通常
you would say he bleached his hair.
你会说他漂白了头发。
And so we understand that it turned white.
所以我们明白头发变白了。
Exactly.
没错。
So those five words we just looked at in language takeaway, they're important.
所以我们在“语言要点”中刚看的这五个词很重要。
They're related to doing laundry.
它们都和洗衣服有关。
So before we move on, let's listen to our dialogue again, but a little bit slower.
所以在继续之前，让我们再听一遍对话，但这次慢一点。
Okay.
好的。
Let's go through this one more time.
我们再过一遍。
I don't want any more ruined or dyed blouses.
我不想再有被洗坏或染色的衬衫了。
I know.
我知道。
Okay.
好的。
So I have to separate the colors from the whites and put them in this strange looking
所以我得把彩色衣服和白色衣服分开，然后放进这个看起来
contraption so-called washing machine.
奇怪的装置里，也就是所谓的洗衣机。
Right.
对。
You have to turn it on and program it depending on what type of clothes you are washing.
你得打开它，根据你洗的衣服类型来设置程序。
For example, for delicates, you should set a shorter washing cycle.
比如，对于精致衣物，你应该设置一个较短的洗涤周期。
Also, be sure to use fabric softener and this detergent when washing.
还有，洗的时候一定要用衣物柔顺剂和这种洗衣粉。
So complicated.
真复杂。
Okay.
好的。
What about this red wine stain?
那这个红酒渍怎么办？
How do I get it out?
我怎么把它弄掉？
Since this is a white t-shirt, you can just pour a little bit of bleach on it and it will
因为这是件白T恤，你可以倒一点漂白剂在上面，
do the trick.
就能搞定了。
Cool.
酷。
Then I can just throw everything in the dryer for an hour and it's all set, right?
那我就可以把所有东西扔进烘干机烘一个小时，就都好了，对吧？
No.
不。
Since you are washing delicates and cotton, you should set the dryer to medium heat and
因为你在洗精致衣物和棉质衣物，你应该把烘干机设为中温，
for 20 minutes.
烘20分钟。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'll just have everything dry clean.
我还是都拿去干洗吧。
So here at EnglishPod, we'd like to also provide you listeners with some phrases that allow
所以在EnglishPod，我们还想为听众提供一些短语，让你
you to increase your fluency.
能提高流利度。
That means sound more like a native English speaker.
也就是说，听起来更像母语为英语的人。
And so today, let's check out these phrases in Fluency Builder.
所以今天，让我们看看“流利度构建”中的这些短语。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
All right.
好的。
So on Fluency Builder, we're going to be looking at four words or four phrases.
所以在“流利度构建”中，我们要看四个词或四个短语。
So the first one was really easy when she was telling the guy or instructing him how
第一个很简单，当她告诉那个家伙或指导他如何
to do the laundry, she said, let's go through this one more time.
洗衣服时，她说：“我们再过一遍。”
Go through what?
穿过什么？
The wall?
墙吗？
No.
不。
So it's not actually to go through an object, like to pass.
所以实际上不是穿过一个物体，像通过。
So it's let's repeat or let's rehearse again.
所以它的意思是重复或再演练一遍。
Okay.
好的。
So normally we say this when there are many different steps to do something.
所以通常我们在做某事有很多不同步骤时会这么说。
So let's go through this again.
所以让我们再过一遍。
When you leave work, you go home, you unlock the door, you open the door.
你下班后，回家，开门锁，开门。
And then so it means that there's a process.
然后这意味着有一个过程。
There are many steps.
有很多步骤。
And so let's go through this again is a way for us to say let's think about and discuss
所以“让我们再过一遍”是一种说法，意思是让我们思考并讨论
this process.
这个过程。
Very good.
很好。
So we also use it maybe when we're studying.
所以我们在学习时也可能用到它。
So let's go through this subject one more time.
所以让我们再复习一遍这个主题。
Can we go through chapter five again?
我们能再过一遍第五章吗？
So you would reread a chapter five.
所以你会重读第五章。
All right.
好的。
So why don't we listen to a couple of more examples of how we could use go through.
那我们再听几个关于如何使用“go through”的例子吧。
Example one.
例子一。
I want to go through chapter five again before the exam tomorrow.
我想在明天考试前再过一遍第五章。
Example two.
例子二。
David, do you have time this afternoon to go over the details of this new project?
大卫，你今天下午有时间讨论这个新项目的细节吗？
Example three.
例子三。
I went through my contract and it says that I am entitled to 15 vacation days a year.
我仔细看了我的合同，上面说我每年有15天带薪假期。
Now this next phrase is very common when we're using sarcasm, when we're trying to make jokes.
接下来这个短语在我们用讽刺语气开玩笑时很常见。
So we say so-called.
我们会说“所谓的”。
Right.
对。
So she said this so-called contraption.
所以她说这个所谓的玩意儿。
It's like she doubts that it's really a washing machine.
就好像她怀疑那是不是真的洗衣机。
So I could say her so-called boyfriend wants to go out tonight.
所以我可以说她所谓的男朋友今晚想出去。
So I say that because he doesn't really act like a boyfriend.
我这么说是因为他表现得不像个男朋友。
So you're being sarcastic.
所以你在讽刺。
It's a very good way and easy way of demonstrating sarcasm.
这是一种很好也很简单的表达讽刺的方式。
Yeah.
是的。
Actually, in the 1990s in America, there was a very famous TV show called My So-Called
实际上，在20世纪90年代的美国，有一部非常著名的电视剧叫《我所谓的》
Life.
生活。
All right.
好的。
So this is my so-called life.
所以这就是我所谓的生活。
It's almost like it's not really like I have any control over it.
就好像我根本控制不了它。
Or I don't really have a life because it's kind of boring.
或者我其实没什么生活，因为它挺无聊的。
Yeah.
是的。
So my so-called life, not bragging.
所以我所谓的生活，不是炫耀。
It's a joke.
这是个玩笑。
So you can say my so-called friends, my so-called job.
所以你可以说我所谓的朋友，我所谓的工作。
Basically, you can almost be sarcastic with anything.
基本上，你几乎可以对任何事讽刺。
Yeah.
是的。
But be careful that you know that it's a joke because if you're trying to be serious, you
但要小心，你得知道这是个玩笑，因为如果你试图认真，
might make some people angry.
可能会惹恼一些人。
Right.
对。
And now, well, she was explaining the whole process of how to do it.
现在，她正在解释整个操作过程。
And when she recommended using bleach, she said that should do the trick.
当她建议用漂白剂时，她说那应该能解决问题。
Trick.
诀窍。
So dogs do tricks, right?
所以狗会耍把戏，对吧？
Right.
对。
But to do the trick, right?
但“do the trick”呢？
What is she saying?
她在说什么？
So it's got a different meaning.
所以它有不同含义。
All right.
好的。
So she's basically saying this should work.
所以她基本上是在说这应该管用。
This should fix your problem.
这应该能解决你的问题。
So that should do the trick.
所以那应该能解决问题。
So Marco, I've been having this itch on my foot and I just can't seem to figure out what
所以马可，我脚上一直痒，但就是不知道
to do with it.
该怎么办。
Do you have any suggestions?
你有什么建议吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You should maybe just put some ointment on it and that should do the trick.
你也许可以涂点药膏，那应该能解决问题。
All right.
好的。
Cool.
酷。
Thanks for the suggestion.
谢谢你的建议。
Yeah.
是的。
So very easy.
所以很简单。
It's just a way of saying that should solve your problem.
这只是一种表达“那应该能解决你的问题”的方式。
All right.
好的。
Great.
很好。
So that's the trick or it will do the trick.
所以那就是诀窍，或者它会管用。
And well, we have one last phrase, all set.
好了，我们还有最后一个短语，“都准备好了”。
All set.
都准备好了。
So this is another phrase that has two words that always go together to mean, well, we're
所以这是另一个由两个词组成的短语，总是一起出现，意思是，嗯，我们
finished.
完成了。
We're done.
我们搞定了。
Everything is ready.
一切都准备好了。
We're all set to go on vacation.
我们都准备好去度假了。
So my bags are packed.
所以我的行李都打包好了。
I have my passports.
我带了护照。
We are all set.
我们都准备好了。
Or after a meeting, you can say, are we all set here?
或者在会议结束后，你可以说，我们这里都准备好了吗？
That means, are we finished?
意思是，我们结束了吗？
Is it time to leave?
该走了吗？
Very good.
非常好。
So we are almost all set.
所以我们差不多都准备好了。
Let's listen to this dialogue one last time.
让我们最后再听一遍这段对话。
Okay.
好的。
Let's go through this one more time.
我们再过一遍。
I don't want any more ruined or dyed blouses.
我不想再有被洗坏或染色的衬衫了。
I know.
我知道。
Okay.
好的。
So I had to separate the colors from the whites and put them in this strange looking contraption
所以我得把彩色衣服和白色衣服分开，然后放进这个看起来怪怪的玩意儿里，
so-called washing machine.
所谓的洗衣机。
Right.
对。
You have to turn it on and program it depending on what type of clothes you're washing.
你得打开它，根据你洗的衣服类型来设定程序。
For example, for delicates, you should set a shorter washing cycle.
比如，对于精致衣物，你应该设置较短的洗涤周期。
Also, be sure to use fabric softener and this detergent when washing.
还有，洗的时候一定要用柔顺剂和这种洗涤剂。
So complicated.
真复杂。
Okay.
好的。
What about this red wine stain?
那这个红酒渍呢？
How do I get it out?
我怎么去掉它？
Since this is a white T-shirt, you can just pour a little bit of bleach on it and it will
因为这是件白T恤，你可以倒一点漂白剂在上面，它就能
do the trick.
解决问题。
Cool.
酷。
Then I can just throw everything in the dryer for an hour and it's all set, right?
那我就可以把所有东西扔进烘干机烘一小时，就都搞定了，对吧？
No.
不。
If you're washing delicates and cotton, you should set the dryer to medium heat and for
如果你洗的是精致衣物和棉质衣物，你应该把烘干机设为中温，
20 minutes.
烘20分钟。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'll just have everything dry cleaned.
我还是把所有东西都送去干洗吧。
Have you ever had any laundry mishaps?
你洗衣服时出过什么意外吗？
Have you ever lost a sock, dyed something?
你丢过袜子，或者把衣服染过色吗？
Have I ever.
当然有过。
I hate doing the laundry.
我讨厌洗衣服。
Why?
为什么？
So much.
太讨厌了。
It's time consuming.
太费时间了。
It takes a lot of time and I just have no patience.
它花很多时间，而且我根本没耐心。
And so normally, when I was in college, I would take all of my laundry in a bag and
所以通常，我上大学的时候，会把所有衣服装进一个袋子，
I'd throw it in the washing machine and I'd put it on cold.
扔进洗衣机，然后设定冷水洗。
Because cold water, it's okay for all colors, but hot water makes the colors bleed.
因为冷水对所有颜色都安全，但热水会让颜色褪色。
I took out the clothes and put them in the dryer and afterwards I saw all my clothes
我把衣服拿出来放进烘干机，之后发现所有衣服
were clean except for my three sweaters, which were small enough for babies.
都干净了，除了三件毛衣，它们小到婴儿都能穿。
Oh, you shrunk it.
哦，你把它们洗缩水了。
I shrunk three brand new sweaters.
我把三件新毛衣洗缩水了。
The problem that I have when doing laundry is that I forget that I started doing laundry.
我洗衣服时的问题是，我忘了自己开始洗衣服了。
So all of a sudden, I'm doing laundry in the morning and then clothes are washed, but they're
所以突然之间，我早上洗衣服，衣服洗好了，但
still in the washing machine.
还留在洗衣机里。
And I remember the next day.
然后我第二天才想起来。
So then the clothes are smelling kind of humid.
所以衣服闻起来有点潮。
Because they're moldy.
因为它们发霉了。
So I have to rewash them and it's just a pain.
所以我得重新洗，真是麻烦。
And doing laundry is sometimes so time consuming, but let us know what you think.
洗衣服有时很费时间，但让我们知道你的想法。
Do you like doing laundry or have you ever lost a sock?
你喜欢洗衣服吗，或者有没有丢过袜子？
I think everyone has lost a sock or something in the washing, right?
我想每个人都丢过袜子之类的东西在洗衣机里，对吧？
I don't know what happens.
我也不知道怎么回事。
I think there's a secret home for socks somewhere.
我觉得袜子有个秘密的家在某个地方。
It's so weird.
真是太奇怪了。
Maybe it's in Australia or something.
也许在澳大利亚之类的地方。
So come to our website, EnglishPod.com.
所以来我们的网站 EnglishPod.com 吧。
Give us all your feedback, questions, comments or suggestions.
给我们所有的反馈、问题、评论或建议。
And we're always there.
我们一直都在那里。
All right.
好的。
Hope to hear from you soon.
希望很快收到你的消息。
And until next time, everyone.
下次再见，各位。
Bye.
拜拜。